(Penny:)I know it sounds
like a cliché,
(Penny:)but compromise is key.
(Leonard:)Never leave a belt
on the floor.
(Leonard:)At night, they
look like snakes.
(Penny:)Do little things, like bring her
a cup of coffee in bed.
(Leonard:)Keep M&M'S in your pocket
(Leonard:)in case you have to
wait in a long line.
(Penny:)You're gonna be seeing
each other a lot,
(Penny:)so respect each other's
personal space.
(Leonard:)He startles easily, so,
please, no flash photography.
(Sheldon:)How many pairs of underwear
did you pack for the move?
(Amy:)I don't know. I didn't count.
(Sheldon:)You truly are the Goofus
to my Gallant.
(Amy:)That's me. Listen,
(Amy:)you and I are gonna
be sharing a bed.
(Amy:)You know, this is uncharted
territory for both of us.
(Amy:)How are you feeling about that?
(Sheldon:)Oh, excited, concerned,
(Sheldon:)a little scared.
(Sheldon:)All the same emotions
(Sheldon:)I feel
in line at Space Mountain.